export default  [
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Github tool can detect vulnerabilities in the dependencies of your Github repository?",
    "correct_answer": "Dependabot",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Github copilot",
        "Github scanning",
        "Vulneracheck",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Artifacts?",
    "correct_answer": "A way to store data produced by a workflow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A cloud storage solution from Github",
        "A place to store source code",
        "A solution for an open issue",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Actions?",
    "correct_answer": "A platform that allows you to automate CI/CD (Build, Test, Deployment), and react to other GitHub events.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A bot that helps you improve your DevOps Automation",
        "A tool that helps you take action on security issues inside your codebase.",
        "An AI pair programmer",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What tool can help you create a quick and consistent development environment?",
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Codespaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "GitHub Copilot",
        "GitHub Actions",
        "GitHub Container Registry",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What tool can help you write code much quicker?",
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Copilot",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "GitHub Codespaces",
        "GitHub Actions",
        "GitHub Container Registry",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "GitHub secret scanning is available",
    "correct_answer": "on private repos with GitHub Advanced Security and public repos on github.com",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Only private repos on github.com",
        "GitHub Enterprise Server",
        "Only public repos on github.com"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Is it possible to create a GitHub Action workflow which reacts to GitHub Issue events (e.g. opened, new comment, closed)?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "No",
        "Only on GitHub Enterprise Cloud",
        "Only with GitHub-hosted runners"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is InnerSource?",
    "correct_answer": "Bringing Open Source Practices to our internal development (e.g. removing silos)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "An early phase of Open Source Adoption",
        "When code is locked down to the teams that need it",
        "A program used to build an Open Source community internally (e.g. drive usage adoption in a secure way, encourage contributions, recognition for OSS work among employees, etc.)"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is GitHub Copilot Workspace?",
    "correct_answer": "A Copilot-native developer environment",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A space where you can build copilots",
        "The next version of GitHub Copilot",
        "An addition to GitHub Codespaces"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Techorama",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "It's the xth birthday of Techorama",
    "correct_answer": "10th",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "7th",
        "12th",
        "9th"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Techorama",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the theme of Techorama 2023?",
    "correct_answer": "Jungle",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pirates",
        "Las Vegas",
        "90's"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Microsoft",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Who is the CEO of Microsoft?",
    "correct_answer": "Satya Nadella",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bill Gates",
        "Thomas Dohmke",
        "Sundar Pichai"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "faq",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How much does Microsoft invest annually in cybersecurity?",
    "correct_answer": "1B USD",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "100K USD",
        "10B USD",
        "100M USD"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "OpenAI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "When was the GPT3 model released?",
    "correct_answer": "2020",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2016",
        "2021",
        "2023"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "OpenAI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How large is the dataset of GPT3?",
    "correct_answer": "GPT-3 is trained on 750 gigabites of data",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "GPT-3 is trained on 200 gigabites of data",
        "GPT-3 is trained on 500 gigabites of data",
        "GPT-3 is tained on 1 petabyte of data"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "OpenAI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "On how many GPUs was the GPT3 model trained?",
    "correct_answer": "This information is not disclosed",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "50000 GPUs",
        "8192 GPUs",
        "3000 GPUs"
      ]
  }
]